COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
Hey, you!
Are you sure you want
to look like that?
Yes, of course!
C'mon! So hurry hurry!
Don't regret it later.
Say cheese!
I Am Konohamaru!
I couldn't decide on how to look.
It took me 3 hours to decide.
But as you can see,
it's more like a work of art.
Doesn't it look great?
Take it over.
What?!
Stop saying that!
Transform!
Oh please, Hokage-sama...
The Sexy Jutsu...
That's quite a devious technique.
By the way Naruto,
where's your headband?
I won't wear it until the orientation.
It might get scratched
Well, that's just fine.
But the Ninja Registration Form
is a very important document
held in high regard by our village.
Why do you want to look like this?
Because!
Anyway, how should I know
about all that stuff?
Old man!
Get ready to fight!
I am going to be the Fifth Hokage!
Ouch!
If it's not one thing, it's another...
Drat! Is this a trap?
Are you okay,
honorable Grandson?
May I just inform you that
there aren't any traps here...
Huh? What's with this runt?
What?!
I know this kid...
He's that Nine-Tailed boy!
He's a good-for-nothing scoundrel!
You must have done this to me!
You tripped all by yourself, stupid!
Hey! Let go of him!
He is the honorable Grandson
of Hokage-sama!
He stopped as soon as
he learned who I am...
He's like my four-eyed teacher.
He's just like everyone else!
What's the matter?
Weren't you gonna hit me, huh?
Can't do it 'cuz
I'm the Hokage's grandson, eh?
As if I care!
Imbecile!
This guy...
What?!
Good grief...
Listen to me.
You are the honorable Grandson
of Hokage-sama.
Even though that scoundrel hit you,
you must not associate with his kind.
Nothing good will come of
your tangling with him.
This is your distinguished
teacher Ebisu,
and I am never wrong
about these things!
Don't you want to become
the Fifth Hokage?
Then allow me
to teach you Ninjutsu,
so that your dream will
become a reality.
That's right.
Stick with me and you will gain a shortcut
towards becoming the Fifth Hokage.
Is that clear, honorable Grandson?
He's gone!
It seems he's gone after Naruto.
Oh no!
This is terrible!
Honorable Grandson!
How did he become like this?
That was the 20th sneak attack today.
And now he's in the company of Naruto.
I'm a bit worried.
I just hope he doesn't pick up
more foolishness.
Huh?
Stop following me!
What is it now?!
Your camouflage is pathetic.
You've seen through my disguise...
Your reputation is well-earned.
I will allow you to make me
your apprentice.
But you must first teach me that
"Sexy Jutsu" technique
you used to beat Grandpa Hokage.
You gotta be kidding.
I beg you to say yes, boss!
Huh?
Boss?
Boss! Boss! Boss!
I guess I have no choice.
Listen.
In order to become a skilled Ninja,
you must first learn to
control your Chatora.
Chatora?
Yes, Chatora.
Boss, I think you mean Chakra.
Silence!
That's what real Ninja call it!
Oh! I didn't know that!
Whew... I'm glad he's a fool.
Listen. Chakra essentially means...
Basically, it is the energy needed
in order to use Jutsu.
Huh?
In other words, fundamentally Ninja Arts
combine the Chakra,
the physical energy accumulated
from each cell in the body
with spiritual energy intensified
through training and experience.
This combined energy is summoned
with certain hand signs.
You made me think
you knew all that,
when you were just reading
from a scroll!
Much has been said about
perfecting the Ninja techniques,
but it really boils down
to just one thing.
And what is that?
Hard work and guts.
Hard work and guts?
That's right.
So be ready for the challenging tasks
I will give you.
Yes, boss!
Good. Let's start right now.
Transform for me.
Huh?
Let me see first
how much you already know.
But what do I transform into?
Okay... First, transform into that lady.
An easy task, boss.
Transform!
Well, do I look like her?
Uhm... Well, the clothes do and...
And what's so similar
about that?!
Honorable Grandson.
If you will transform into me,
at least try to look a little cuter, okay?
She's scary!
Why am I the one who gets hit?
Okay!
Next, we'll do some research on sexiness!
Yes, boss!
I told you I don't allow
reading here, Naruto!
This is the last test.
Put all of your effort into it!
Yes, boss!
Transform!
Naruto! It's you again!
Why is it always me...?
— Sorry.
— Huh?
It's because
I'm the Hokage's grandson.
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
You're now ready to perform
the Sexy Jutsu!
You just need more practice.
Yes, boss!
Okay, keep in mind...
the point is for "boom boom boom"!
Now do it!
Yes, boss!
Transform!
What do you think?
That won't do!
More slender.
Yes, boss!
Is this okay?
Not yet.
More attractive.
Yes, boss!
How about now?
That Naruto... What is he teaching
the Honorable Grandson...?
Where the hell could they be...?
I am a distinguished teacher
training potential Hokage.
All those who interfere
will be eliminated.
You know I've been wondering...
You seem obsessed with beating
your Grandpa Hokage.
My name is Konohamaru.
It was Grandpa who gave me
that name.
He named me after our village.
It should be easy for everyone
here to remember.
But nobody ever calls me
by that name.
When they see me, all they see
is the Grandson of the Hokage.
No one sees me for who I really am.
I can't stand it anymore.
That's why...
That's why I want the title
of Hokage now.
Idiot... Who do you think
will accept you, huh?
Huh?
You won't win the title
that easily, you know.
What?!
It's not that simple.
If you're really serious about gaining
the title of Hokage...
What?
You'll have to beat me first!
Hokage-sama!
I've been looking for you.
Iruka.
Did Naruto re-submit
his Ninja Registration Form?
Yes.
When I lectured to him the other night
at the ramen stand,
he said he will make everyone accept him
now that he's a Ninja.
He's been happy since then.
It might not be easy for Naruto
to realize that dream.
Huh?
As you well know,
only the villagers who fought
the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit 12 years ago
know that the monster is sealed
inside Naruto.
I ruled that no one shall speak
about that incident.
I have severely punished those
who have broken this rule.
Now our children know nothing about it.
That is the only positive
development for Naruto.
Before the Fourth Hokage trapped
the monster and died,
his last wish was for the villagers
to regard Naruto as a hero.
A hero?
The Fourth Hokage sealed the monster
into the navel of a newborn baby
whose umbilical cord
had just been cut.
As the receptacle
for the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit,
Naruto saved the village.
Unfortunately, the other villagers
don't see him like that.
Some even say that Naruto is
the Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit himself.
Little by little, that attitude has been
passed down to their own children.
Iruka.
Do you know?
What, sir?
When someone is hated and people refuse
to accept his existence,
he sees it in the eyes
of the people around him.
I have found you!
Huh?
That Demon Fox!
That cold look!
It's always like that!
Honorable Grandson,
we have to go now.
No way!
I want to beat Grandpa right now
so I can win the title of Hokage!
Don't get in my way!
A Hokage must first know about virtue,
honor, etiquette, wisdom, loyalty, faith,
judgment, obedience
and all that.
He must be skilled at more than
thousand techniques...
And then...
Transform!
Take this! Sexy Jutsu!
What?
It didn't work!
What kind of a
disgraceful spell is that?!
I am a gentleman!
Such vulgar attacks
will never work on me!
Honorable Grandson!
That rascal will only make you an imbecile!
Stick with me and...
you will gain a shortcut
towards becoming the Fifth Hokage.
C'mon, let's go!
No way!
Shadow Clone Jutsu
Wow!
Fantastic!
Ha!
That's nothing.
I am a distinguished teacher.
I am not as weak as Mizuki.
Boss...
Transform!
Oh, Ebisu-sama...
I call it "the Harem Jutsu"!
He combined the Multiple Clones with
his own Sexy Jutsu.
That's another devious attack.
I probably won't even survive that one.
I can't even beat that
four-eyed teacher of mine!
I want the title of Hokage so badly!
I want to be recognized by everybody!
But I keep failing.
You think it's that easy?
Huh?
It's given only to the greatest Ninja
in the village.
Everybody must learn to believe in you.
I've been through a lot already.
It's been one struggle after another.
But after all that,
I found someone who accepts me.
I had to go through a lot...
Just for one person.
You had better push yourself.
For what?
The path of getting the title,
Hokage, is a brutal one.
There's no such thing as a shortcut.
If you're really serious about
attaining the title of Hokage
You'll have to beat me first.
Who do you think you are,
lecturing me like that?
I won't be your apprentice anymore.
From now on, you're my rival.
Unfortunately for you,
tomorrow I graduate from the Ninja Academy.
Still, I'll consider you an equal someday
when we fight for the title of Hokage.
Let's look forward to that, Konohamaru.
You still have a long way to go
to become a real Ninja.
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
Ahh! Why do I have to be in
the same group with Sasuke?
The guy I hate the most?
Sakura-chan keeps saying
"Sasuke, Sasuke, Sasuke!"
and doesn't even
pay attention to me!
It makes me so mad!
I got it! I'm going to pull one on him!
I'm not gonna let him be so cool
in front of Sakura-chan!
Next Episode:
"A Rival?! Sasuke and Sakura."
Watch my outstanding performance!